ACTWU's Social Services Department Records 5619/023
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Pennsylvania: Allentown Number 1665 Fairtex: Plant Closing, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania: Allentown/ Bethlehem Number 730T, 965T, 1564, 1665, 1895, 2304, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Bangor, Pennsylvania Local 1445-T, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Local 1739, Carlisle, Pennsylvania, Masland Carpet, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh District Joint Board, Connellsville Local 433, Connellsville Sportswear, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Locals 575, 1082, 622 Greene County (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Local 1859, Hanover, Pennsylvania, Revonah Spinning Mills, Garden Spot Joint Board, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- J. Bass and Company, Local 1669 Hazelton, Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Pennsylvania, West Hazelton Number 1732, Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, Futura Fabrics, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- West Hazleton, Pennsylvania Local 238-A, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Huntington, Pennsylvania, Local 1034T, Mid-Atlantic Regional Joint Board, Owens Corning Fiberglass, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania: Meadville Local 8T Avtex Plant Closing, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Greenway Inc. - Nemacolin, Pennsylvania Number 1083, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Pittsburgh (area), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Local 1808, Nesquehoning, Pennsylvania, Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Pennsylvania, Norristown Number 415 T Nicolet Industries, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Pittsburgh District Joint Board (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Pennsylvania: Number 1056, Osceola Mills Plant Closing, Viceroy Manufacturing Company, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Pennsylvania: Number 208 T Philadelphia Plant Closing, Peerless Dye Works, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Pennsylvania: Pine Grove and Auburn Number 1493, 1559, and 1785, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh District Joint Board, Local 86-A - Advo, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Local 1493 - Pine Grove, Pennsylvania, Mid-Atlantic Joint Board (Allentown) - Gold Mills, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Shamoken, Pennsylvania - Lewistown, Pennsylvania (Cluett Peabody), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Smethport, Pennsylvania Pittsburgh District - Jaguar Manufacturing (Target), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Pennsylvania: Valley Forge Number 1369 Plant Closing, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Pennsylvania Atwater Number 998T Wilkes-Barre Native Textile 1824 (Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board), 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Quin State Region Social Services, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Central Falls, Rhode Island - Local 615 New England Region Joint Board - Healthtex, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board Textile Division, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Anderson, South Carolina - Local 1833 West Carolinas Joint Board - True Temper, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Social Services South Carolina, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- South Carolina: Andrews Number 1900 Oneita Knitting Mills, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- J. P. Stevens Allendale, South Carolina Local 2377, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Local 1950 - Belton, South Carolina, Western Carolinas Joint Board - Belton Corporation, 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- South Carolina: Charleston Raybestos Manhattan Industry Products Number 1836 Coastal Joint Board, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Local 503 - Levi Charleston, South Carolina, Carolinas/Virginia Region Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- South Carolina: Columbia Number 253 Mount Vernon Inc. Closing, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- South Carolina, Columbia Local 254, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- South Carolina - Darlington Mills, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Social Services Greenville, South Carolina, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- South Carolina: Johnsonville Number 2398 Wellman Industries South Carolina Joint Board, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Local 675, Newberry, South Carolina, Hypertension, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Local 675 Newberry, South Carolina, South Region Joint Board, Damon International, 1981-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- South Carolina: Orangeburg Number 1147, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- South Carolina, Pamlico, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Local 710T Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Local 2397, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- South Carolina: Woodruff Number 1075, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Tennessee: GTA Joint Board Credit Union Number 2408, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Tennessee: Knoxville GTA Joint Board General, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Tennessee: Bemis Number 281 Tennessee Textiles, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Local 1418 - Chattanooga, Tennessee, GTA Area Joint Board, SCT Yarn, Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Tennessee: Columbia Number 1006 (Plant Closing) West Central Joint Board, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Crossville, Tennessee Local 2349, Munsingwear Southeastern Regional Clothing Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Tennessee: Knoxville Number 664 (C) Knoxville Manufacturing Plant Closed, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Tennessee - Campaign Local 996 Levi Strauss, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Knoxville, Tennessee - Local 1742 GTA Area Joint Board - Allied Signal, 1976-1986 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Local 2424 Southern Region, Knoxville, Tennessee, London Fog, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Ohio: Cleveland Joint Board Social Services Committee (Clothing), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Ohio: Ohio State Joint Board, 1977-1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Ohio: Cleveland Joint Board Number 1448 Phoenix Dye, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Ohio, Findlay, Local 1812, Toledo Joint Board - Kuss Corporation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Ohio - Greenville Local 941C, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Ohio, Hamilton (Plant Closing) Lesner Corporation Number 148, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Ohio: Local 1902 - Middlefield, Ohio State Joint Board, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Ohio: Painesville Number 482 (Plant Closing project American Cyanamid (T) Synthetics Division, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Ohio, Toledo, Local 226T Inmont Corporation, Ohio State Joint Board, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Youngstown, Ohio Local 191 Pittsburgh District Joint Board - Weatherbee, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Oregon: Portland Social Services Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Pennsylvania: Lehigh Valley Joint Board, Allentown Social Service Conference, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Pennsylvania: Keystone Joint Board: General Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Pennsylvania: Allentown, Pennsylvania Keystone Joint Board Credit Union, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board, Pottsville, Pennsylvania, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Philadelphia Social Service Committee Plans, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Pennsylvania: Philadelphia Clothing Joint Board: Social Services, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Philadelphia Joint Board/ Textile Division, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Pine Grove Pennsylvania: Childcare Project, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Local 2410, Pennsylvania Joint Board, Pottsville, Pennsylvania Target, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Pennsylvania Pittsburg Joint Board, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Tennessee, Lebanon Woolen Mills - Organizing, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Tennessee: Maryville Number 1933, Schlegel Tennessee Inc. EAP Human Services Program, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Local 965 Memphis, Levi Strauss, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Tennessee, Memphis Local 1782, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Texas, Del Rio Local 2285, Social Services Department, Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- El Paso Joint Board, Texas, 1975-1988 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- San Antonio Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- San Antonio Joint Board/ Humanities, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Carrizo Springs, Texas Local 1174, Southern Regional Joint Board, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Local 2294 San Antonio Joint Board, Eagle Pass, Texas, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Texas: Laredo Number 2287 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- San Antonio, Texas, Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1980-1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Local 982 C Brigham City, Utah Colorado District Joint Board, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Virginia: Abingdon Social Services, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Local 704, Danville, Virginia 24541, Social Service Committee, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Virginia, Front Royal Local 371/1757 Avtex Social Services, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Virginia: Blackstone Local 2330 Mid-Atlantic Joint Board, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Virginia: Charlottesville Number 672, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Christiansburg, Virginia Local 2491 California/Virginia (s. Reg.) - Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Local 704 Danville, Virginia Carolinas - Virgina Regional Joint Board, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Local 1841 - Dillwyn, Virginia Mid-Atlantic Region, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Drakes Branch, Virginia, Roanoke Valley Joint Board, J. P. Stevens, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Virginia: Elkton Number 1380 Strike, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Local 713T - Fredericksburg, Virginia, Steel Pak Rappahannock Joint Board, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Local 371, 1757T Front Royal, Virginia AVTEX, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Virginia: Petersburg Number 1178 Mass Lay-off, Carolina/Virginia Region Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Virginia: Upper South Region Joint Board, Galax: Wonderknit/ Hanes, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Virginia: Number 2024 Narrows, Virginia, Social Services, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Virginia: Norfolk Stylemaster Inc., 1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Local 2492 Petersburg, Virginia, Carolina/Virginia Region Office (S. Reg.) Healthtex, 1973-1987 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Virginia, Pulaski Local 2417, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Virginia: Richmond Number 88 Friedman-Marks Closing, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Virginia, Springfield, Xerox Local 14R, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Williamsburg, Virginia Mid-Atlantic Region Joint Board, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Virginia: Wytheville 2414, Lay-off, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Pacific North West Joint Board, Yakima, Washington, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Pacific Northwest Joint Board, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- West Coast Region Joint Board, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Albright, West Virginia Local 217A (Shoe) Kinney Shoe, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- West Virginia, Nitro Local 7 and 1765 AVTEX Synthetics Division, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Summersville, West Virginia - Local 206 A Pittsburg District Joint Board - Carroll Shoe, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- West Virginia: Local 347 Morgantown, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Pittsburgh, Scranton - Wilkes-Barre, West Virginia Region Joint Board, Local 2392, Summersville, West Virginia, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Wisconsin, Ashland Number 1259 Social Services, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Wyoming: Cheyenne, Number 1123 Social Service Committee, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Southern Labor Articles, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- J. P. Stevens, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Roanoke Rapids, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Greenville, South Carolina, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- GEB Committee on Unemployed ACTWU Members Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Aid Fund Correspondence, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Alejandro Duhalde, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Terresa Tyake, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Margarita Caret, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Unemployed Lists of Shoe Workers (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Gloversville Time Sheets, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Gloversville Ontaraca, Time Sheets, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Syracuse Outreach, William Guinn, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Grant Hours Diana Depugh Kurnik, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Grant Hours Diana Depugh-Kurnik, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Greenville/Industrial, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Greenville, South Carolina, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Greenville, South Carolina, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Greenville, South Carolina, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Greenville, South Carolina, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- United Labor Service Agency, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Greenville Board/ Finance Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Greenville, South Carolina United Labor Service Agency, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Greenville, South Carolina Workshops and Services, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- United Labor Service Agency Ruth Antoniades, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- United Labor Services Agency Case Illustrations, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- United Labor Service Agency Greenville Conference, 1967-1979 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- ULSA United Way Application, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- ULSA Greenville Bills, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- AFL-CIO Ruth Antoniades, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Lease, 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Emergency Funding - ULSA, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- United Service Labor Agency, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Approved Modification Number 1, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Approved Modification Number 2 Shoe Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Shoe Worker Reachout - ACTWU Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- New York State AFL-CIO, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- A-V Equipment, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Computer, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Shoeworker - DOL Meetings/Memos, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- DOL- Letters, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Evaluacione, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Spanish; English
- Glove City, New York Leatherworkers, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Shoeworker - Job Description Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Match Money, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- MIS/ corrected copies, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Shoe Originals (Modification Number 1), 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Shoeworker - Originals, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Pier, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Peer Outreach Workers, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Planning Grant, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Shoeworker - Planning Notes, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Reports/ Statistics, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Employee Monthly Report, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  Spanish
- SER, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Syracuse, New York Nettleton Follow-up, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Mision: Empleo Travel/Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Conference Packets, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Mission Empleo, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- ACTWU Shoeworkers, Mission Empleo Staff Time Sheets, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 1-25, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 26-50, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 51-75, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 76-96, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 97-114, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 115-139, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 140-158, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 159-188, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 189-220, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 221-252, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 253-288, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 1-25, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 26-50, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 51-75, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Unemployment Aid Fund, No. 76-110, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Unemployment Aid Fund Contributors, A-C, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Unemployment Aid Fund Contributors, D-H, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Unemployment Aid Fund Contributors, I-P, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Unemployment Aid Fund Contributors, Q-Z, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Pentagon Papers Top Secret, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  June
- Tomei, Vincent, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Szpak, Michael, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  2 photographs
- Prero, Alissa Eve, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Skubi, Wilfred, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Senturia, Alice, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Parsh, Jerry, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Seiter, Julie, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Farah-San Antonio, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Farah Social Studies, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Farah Publicity, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Retired Members' Letters, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Farah-Memos to Jack Sheinkman, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Farah-Overseas, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Farah Poling, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Farah-Holiday Fund, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Farah Leaflets, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Farah-General, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Farah-Letters of Support, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Farah-Strike General, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Farah Citizens Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Justice, Barbara, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Retired Members' Letters, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Magarik, Larry, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Southern California Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Farah Student Committees, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Alissa Prero- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Thompson, Patricia, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Leslie Nader, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Carolyn Schmitz, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Nell Merlino. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Mary Reyna, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Farah Christmas Cards, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Amalgamated Student Program, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Micheal J. Cavan. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Robert Gaw. Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Jerry Parsh-Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Farah Contributions, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Farah Film, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Young, Jackie, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Zeirner, Bronwen, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Farah Adopt a Family, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Farah- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Farah Boycott- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- No. A-9 Amalgamated Retiree Services (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Merlino, Nell, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Gaw, Robert, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Gonzales, Hector F., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Hoover, Linda, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Jacobs, Ellis, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Friedman, Jeff, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Davidson, Terri, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Conason, Joseph J., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Cavanaugh, Michael J., 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Ballinger, Jeff, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Farah Students A. [1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Farah Students A. [2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Personal, 1964-1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  8 photographs
- Personal 1972, 1962-1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Speeches, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Jacob S. Potofsky and Frank Rosenblum Retirement Dinner, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  January, 13
- Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women- National Executive Board, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Women I, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Women I, 1972-1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Cornell Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Retired Members Letters, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Retiree Mail III, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Committees, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing workers of America-Aiding Jobless, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America-Age, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- National Health Insurance (No.1 in series) (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Full Employment (No.2 in series) (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Imports (No.3 in series) (Box 10, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens (No.4 in series) (Box 10, Folder 10)
- National Labor Relations Act (No.5 in series) (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Era (No.6 in series) (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Civil Liberties (No.7 in series) (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Civil Rights (No.8 in series) (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Political Action (No.9 in series) (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Organizing (No.10 in series) (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Canada (No.11 in series) (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Fair Labor Standards Act (No.12 in series) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Canada and Imports (No.13 in series) [folder 1 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Canada and Imports (No.13 in series) [folder 2 of 2] (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Convention Resolutions, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Advertising Request Frere Arbitre, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  Yiddish and English
- Advertising Workmens circle, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Advertising Request Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- I.U.E. Strike (Photograph), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  1 photograph, January
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Associate Members Organization, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- American Bar Association, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Staff Meetings, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Industries, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Per Capita, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Per Capita, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Membership, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1974-1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cope Report, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  February
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Convention, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council Minutes, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Council Minutes, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Financial Statements, 1981-1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations Committee on Union Retirees, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Member Benefit Kit, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Legal, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees Insurance Fund, Trustees Meeting, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees' Retirement Income Plan, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  July 1
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees' Insurance Fund, Minutes, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company, Auditor's Report, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Life and Health Insurance Company, Director's meeting, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Finances, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)